Guide to the Hisham Khatib Collection of photographic prints AD.MC.030
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Egypt and Yemen, Circa 1867-1900; ref721 (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
  - No.136 Saqqarah Pyramides (A view of the Saqqara Pyramids)., Circa 1880s; ref342; Béchard, Émile, Circa 1860-1880; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Saqqara, Egypt; Deserts; Pyramids; French Writing; Men; Regional/National Dress; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - 204 Oran - Le Port, vue prise de la Promenade de Létang (A view of the Port of Oran taken from the Promenade de Létang)., Circa 1870-1900; ref343; Etablissements Photographiques de Neurdein Freres (ND Phot), Paris (France); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Ports; Boats/Ships; Seas; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Streets/Roads; French Writing; Landscapes; Oran, Algeria
  - Laghouat, La place du marché (The marketplace in Laghouat, Algeria)., Circa 1870-1900; ref344; Etablissements Photographiques de Neurdein Freres (ND Phot), Paris (France); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Palm Trees; Buildings; Men; Women; Children; Streets/Roads; Laghouat, Algeria; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress
  - A mummified head of Ramses II from Deir El Bahri, Egypt., Circa 1881; ref345; Brugsch, Émile; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; Thebes, Egypt
  - Kairo, Les Pyramides, Femmes Arabes (Women drawing water with the Pyramids in the background)., Circa 1870-1930; ref346; Photoglob Co. (Zurich, Switzerland).; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Women; Palm Trees; Pyramids; Cairo, Egypt; Animals; Camels; Nile River; Rivers; Albumen Prints; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Giza, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Landscapes
  - 5554 Thebes Tombeau de Nekht peinture (A wall painting at the Theban Tomb of Nakht)., Circa 1891-1914; ref347; Photoglob Co. (Zurich, Switzerland).; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Thebes, Egypt; French Writing; Tombs/Mausoleums; Paintings; Men; Women; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites
  - 5563 Thebes Tombeau de Rehmara (barque sacré) (A painting of a sacred boat at Theban Tomb of Rehmara)., Circa 1891-1914; ref348; Photoglob Co. (Zurich, Switzerland).; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Thebes, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Paintings; French Writing; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Men; Women; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites
  - Aden, General View, No.2 (A view of Aden, Yemen)., Circa 1870-1900; ref349; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Buildings; Aden, Yemen; Streets/Roads
  - No. 45 The Crescent (Aden)., Circa 1870-1900; ref350; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; English Writing; Buildings; Aden, Yemen; Streets/Roads; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation
- Bexhill Family Series, February 1908; ref722 (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
  - Two young girls running in El Mehalla, Egypt / little girl in white dress in Bexhill, East Sussex, England., February 1908; ref351; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Girls; Children; Men; Buildings; Hats; El Mahalla El Kubra, Egypt; Houses; Bexhill, England, UK
  - Two young girls standing among sacks and reverse in group portraits in El Mehalla, Egypt., February 1908; ref352; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; El Mahalla El Kubra, Egypt; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Women; Men; Children; Girls; Hats; Animals; English Writing
  - A street with pedestrians., February 1908; ref368; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Buildings; Men; Architecture; Shops; Streets/Roads; Unknown Locations; Street Lamps
  - A side street with shops and stalls., February 1908; ref369; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Streets/Roads; Regional/National Dress; Street Vendors; Buildings; Hats; Shops; Egypt
  - A ship docked at a port., February 1908; ref370; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Ports; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Men; Women; Children; Regional/National Dress; Egypt; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
  - Carriages in front of a railway station., February 1908; ref371; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; Horses; Men; Egypt; Railways; Animals; Bow Ties; Hats; Facial Hair; Streets/Roads
  - A vessel flying the Egyptian flag., February 1908; ref372; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Seas; Landscapes; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Egypt
  - A group of men playing tug of war on the deck of a ship, February 1908; ref373; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Men; Women; Boats/Ships; Hats; Unknown Locations
- Schoolmaster Series, 1933; ref724 (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
  - Men setting up funeral tents., Circa 1933; ref353; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Tents; Funeral Proceedings; Men; Regional/National Dress; English Writing; Egypt
  - A brass band playing to a crowd in a street., Circa 1933; ref354; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Musical Instruments; Men; Women; Children; Boys; Girls; Brass Instruments; Percussion Instruments; Group Portraits; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Egypt; Facial Hair; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
  - A view of a hotel veranda in Ras-el-Bar, Egypt., July 1933; ref355; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; English Writing; Ras al Bar, Damietta, Egypt; Hotels; Buildings; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Hats; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A floating hotel in Ras-el-Bar., July 1933; ref356; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Hotels; Seas; Buildings; English Writing; Ras al Bar, Damietta, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Water
  - Two men sitting on the steps of the Savoy Hotel in Ras-el-Bar., July 1933; ref357; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Animals; Dogs; English Writing; Men; Group Portraits; Hotels; Hats; Ras al Bar, Damietta, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Restaurants/bars
  - Three schoolmasters marking papers., Circa 1933; ref358; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Teachers; Hats; Uniforms; Schools/Education; English Writing; Egypt; Fez/Tarboush
  - A main gate for the masters at a school., Circa 1933; ref359; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Children; Boys; Schools/Education; Transportation; English Writing; Hats; Egypt
  - Students at oral examinations in Shebeen-el-Kom., Circa 1933; ref360; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Men; Schools/Education; English Writing; Buildings; Shibin El Kom, Egypt; Fez/Tarboush; Smoking; Cigarettes; Group Portraits; Students; Facial Hair; Books; Hats
  - The house of a pasha in Mansoura., Circa 1933; ref361; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Mansoura, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Pasha; Street Lamps; Houses
  - A view of Damietta from the Nile., Circa 1933; ref363; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Damietta, Egypt; Nile River; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Houses; Landscapes
  - A man sitting by a mosque door in Mansoura., June 1933; ref364; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Mansoura, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Mosques; Buildings; Religious Sites; Architecture; English Writing; Facial Hair; Royalty
  - A view of the village of Al Baramun, Egypt., Circa 1933; ref365; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Children; Boys; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Mansoura, Egypt
  - A group of men and women having tea at a picnic., Circa 1933; ref366; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Tea/Coffee; Food; Animals; Dogs; Landscapes; Children; Boys; Egypt; Drinks/Beverages; Picnic; Facial Hair
  - A chief of the night watchman, outside a ceremonial tent., Circa 1933; ref367; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only - 030_ref328-ref350)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Hats; Uniforms; Tents; Egypt
- Palestine, Damascus and Lebanon - Bonfils, Circa 1867-1880; ref725 (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
  - 593 - Chamelier du Sinai (A camel driver from Sinai)., Circa 1867-1880; ref376; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Sinai, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; French Writing; Facial Hair
  - 357 - Palestine, Intérieur de l'Eglise de l'Anonciation à Nazareth (A view of the interior of the Church of the Annunciation in Nazareth)., Circa 1867-1880; ref377; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; French Writing; Palestine; Nazareth; Churches; Religious Sites; Architecture; Chandeliers; Italian Writing; Religious Imagery
  - 253 - Jérusalem, Intérieur de l'Ecce Homo (A view of the interior of the Chapel of Ecce Homo in the Convent of Sisters of Zion, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref378; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Statues/Sculptures; Chandeliers; Religious Sites; Churches; Jerusalem; Palestine
  - 904 - Fontaine des Apôtres sur la route de Jéricho (Fountain of the Apostles on the road to Jericho)., Circa 1867-1880; ref379; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Palestine; Jericho; Fountains; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Men; Regional/National Dress; Animals; Horses; Donkeys
  - 415bis - Damas, Intérieur de la grotte d'Ananie (Interior of the Grotto of Ananias in the House of Saint Ananias, Damascus)., Circa 1867-1880; ref380; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Damascus, Syria; Chandeliers; Religious Imagery; Religious Sites; Carpets/Rugs; French Writing; English Writing; Furnishings; Paintings; Religious Crosses; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - 278 - Mosquée d'Omar et tribunal de David (Dome of the Rock, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref381; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings; Religious Sites; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Jerusalem; Palestine; Architecture; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Photographic Prints; Mosques; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Tombs/Mausoleums
  - 414 - Damas, Rue Droite près de Bab-Charki (A street called Straight near the Eastern door of Damascus called Bab-Charki)., Circa 1867-1880; ref382; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Damascus, Syria; Streets/Roads; Men; Animals; Buildings
  - 422 - Damas, Tombeau de Saint-Jean dans la Grande Mosquée (A view of the tomb of Saint John in the Great Mosque, Damascus)., Circa 1867-1880; ref383; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Damascus, Syria; Tombs/Mausoleums; French Writing; Chandeliers; Umayyad Mosque/Great Mosque of Damascus; Religious Sites
  - 376 - Banias, source du Jourdain (Bainas, Caesarea Philippi)., Circa 1867-1880; ref384; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Landscapes; French Writing; English Writing; Mountains/Hills; Jordan River; Caves; Springs; Syria; Mount Hermon/Jabal al-Shaykh, Lebanon
  - A landscape with rocks and trees (Lebanon cedars). Snowy mountains can be seen in the background., Circa 1867-1880; ref385; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Snow; English Writing
  - Lebanon cedars covered in snow in the forest., Circa 1867-1880; ref386; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Landscapes; Forest/Woodlands; Snow; English Writing
  - 16. Vallée des Tombeaux de Josaphat (Valley of Josaphat, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref387; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Landscapes; Jerusalem; French Writing; Buildings; Architecture; Kidron Valley; Tomb of Absalom; Tomb of Zechariah; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites; Palestine; Tomb of Benei Hezir; Church of Mary Magdalene, Jerusalem
  - 303 - Jardin de Gethsemané, vue générale - The garden of Gethsemane, general view., Circa 1867-1880; ref388; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; French Writing; Gardens; Mountains/Hills; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Palestine; Religious Sites; Landscapes; Streets/Roads; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - Fontaine d'Elise - Elisa's fountain., Circa 1867-1880; ref389; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Albumen Prints; Studio Photography; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Men; English Writing; Photographic Prints
  - 918 - Cours et gué du Jourdain - Course and ford of the Jordan., Circa 1867-1880; ref390; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Jordan River; Forest/Woodlands; English Writing; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes
  - 255- Eglise Ste Anne et vue générale de Jérusalem - St Anne's Church and general view of Jerusalem., Circa 1867-1880; ref391; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Churches; Palestine
  - 252 - Arc de l'Ecce Homo - Arch of the Ecce Homo., Circa 1867-1880; ref392; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Jerusalem; Palestine
  - 287- Porte de Damas - The Damascus gate., Circa 1867-1880; ref393; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Damascus Gate, Jerusalem; Palestine; Architecture; Buildings; Forts/Castles; French Writing; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils
  - 288 - Tombeau de David sur le Mont Sion - Tomb of David on Mount Zion., Circa 1867-1880; ref394; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Tombs/Mausoleums; Jerusalem; Palestine; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture
  - 278 - Vue générale de la mosquée d'Omar - General view of the mosque of Omar (Dome of the Rock, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref395; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Jerusalem; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Religious Sites; Men; French Writing; English Writing; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Mosques; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Tombs/Mausoleums
  - 279 - Intérieur de la mosquée Omar, le Rocher - Interior of the Mosque of Omar: The Rock (Dome of the Rock, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref396; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Jerusalem; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - 304 - Jardin de Gethsemané - The Garden of Gethsemane., Circa 1867-1880; ref397; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Men; Regional/National Dress; Architecture; Buildings; Forts/Castles; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Gardens; Individual Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - 274 - Coupoles du St Sépulcre (Cupolas of the church of the Holy Sepulchre, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref398; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Buildings; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Jerusalem; Palestine; French Writing; Architecture; Religious Sites; Churches; Religious Crosses
  - 278 - Mosque Of Omar (A view of the Dome of the Rock)., Circa 1867-1880; ref399; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital Copy Only - 030_ref376-317)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Jerusalem; Palestine; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā
- Palestine by Bonfils, F.M. Good et al, ref726 (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
  - Holy sites in Jerusalem., Circa 1867-1900; ref400; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Palestine; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Churches; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun, Jerusalem; Buildings; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; Church of the Sepulchre of Saint Mary/Tomb of Saint Mary; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
  - 275 - Porte dorée extérieur, Jérusalem (The Golden Gate, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref401; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Jerusalem; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Golden Gate, Jerusalem; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; French Writing
  - 893 - Grotte de la Nativité: la crêche - Cave of the Nativity: the manger (Bethlehem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref402; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Bethlehem; Palestine; Church of the Nativity; Caves; Churches; Tapestry; Religious Sites; Religious Imagery; English Writing; French Writing; West Bank
  - 323 - Pool of Siloe (Pool of Siloam, Silwan)., Circa 1867-1880; ref403; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Siloam/Silwan; Lakes; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Religious Sites; Palestine
  - 344 - Montagne de la Quarantaine - Mount of Temptation., Circa 1867-1880; ref404; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Mount Quarantania/Jabal al-Qarantal, Jericho; West Bank; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; French Writing; English Writing; Jericho; Palestine
  - 851 - Intérieur du St Sépulcre aux ornements (A view of the interior of the Church of the Holy Sepulchre, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1900; ref405; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Men; Group Portraits; Religious Sites; Churches; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Imagery; Statues/Sculptures; Chandeliers; Facial Hair; Priests/Clergymen; Hats; Jerusalem; Palestine
  - A group of people with camels and donkeys., Circa 1867-1880; ref406; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Camels; Animals; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Women; Children; Donkeys
  - 863 Jérusalem. Détails intérieurs de la mosquée El-Aksa (A view of the interior of the Al-Aqsa mosque, Jerusalem)., Circa 1867-1880; ref407; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Jerusalem; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Chandeliers; Mosques; Palestine; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Arabic Calligraphy
  - 297 - Eglise du Pater, intérieur - Church of the Pater Noster., Circa 1867-1880; ref408; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Churches; English Writing; French Writing; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Church of the Pater Noster
  - 417 - Damas. Mur par où Saint Paul s'est enfui (Bab Kisan)., Circa 1867-1880; ref409; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Damascus, Syria; Forts/Castles; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; French Writing; English Writing; Streets/Roads
  - 915 - Halte des voyageurs sur les bords du Jourdain (Resting place of the travellers on the shores of the Jordan river)., Circa 1867-1880; ref410; Bonfils, Felix; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref400-ref421)
    Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; French Writing; Jordan River; Individual Portraits; Rivers; Men; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Bedouins; Facial Hair; Water